seleniumeasy.com 2019-09-27

# Privacy Policy | Selenium Easy

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Selenium Easy collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the [http://seleniumeasy.com](http://seleniumeasy.com/) website ("Site"). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Selenium Easy.

Personal identification data

We might collect personal identification data from Users in a very sort of ways that, including, however not restricted to, once Users visit our website, register on the location, and in reference to different activities, services, options or resources we tend to build on the market on our website. Users could also be asked for, as applicable, name, email address. Users may, however, visit our website anonymously. we are going to collect personal identification data from Users provided that they voluntarily submit such data to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally information, except that it's going to stop them from participating in bound website connected activities.

Non-personal identification data

We might collect non-personal identification data regarding Users whenever they move with our website. Non-personal identification data might embrace the browser name, the sort of pc and technical data regarding Users means that of affiliation to our website, like the OS and therefore the web service providers utilised and other similar information.

Web browser cookies

Our website might use "cookies" to boost User experience. User's browser places cookies on their disk drive for record-keeping functions and generally to trace data regarding them. User might opt to set their browser to refuse cookies, or to provide you with a warning once cookies area unit being sent. If they are doing therefore, note that some elements of the site might not perform properly.

How we tend to use collected information

Selenium easy might collect and use Users personal data for the subsequent purposes:

\- to boost customer service  
Information you give helps America reply to your client service requests and support wants additional expeditiously.  
\- To personalize user expertise  
We might use data within the combination to grasp however our Users as a bunch use the services and resources provided on our website.  
\- to boost our website  
We might use feedback you give to boost our merchandise and services.  
\- To send periodic emails  
We might use the e-mail address to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests.

How we tend to protect your information

We adopt applicable knowledge assortment, storage and process practices and security measures to guard against unauthorized access, alteration, speech act or destruction of your personal data, username, password, dealings data and knowledge keep on our website.

Sharing your personal data

We don't sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification data to others. we may share generic aggregative demographic data not connected to any personal identification data concerning guests and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

Third party websites

Users might notice advertising or different content on our website that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. we don't control the content or links that seem on these sites and aren't accountable for the practices used by websites connected to or from our website. additionally, these sites or services, as well as their content and links, could also be perpetually ever-changing. These sites and services might have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on the other web site, as well as websites that have a link to our website, is subject to it website's own terms and policies.

Google Adsense

Some of the ads could also be served by Google. Google's use of the DART cookie allows it to serve ads to Users supported their visit to our website and different sites on the web. DART uses "non in person acknowledgeable data" and will NOT track personal information regarding you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. you may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

Changes to the present privacy policy

Selenium easy has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we are going to post a notification on the main page of our website, revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. we tend to encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to remain wise regarding however we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it's your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

Your acceptance of these terms

By using this website, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please don't use our website. Your continuing use of the site following the posting of changes to this policy are deemed your acceptance of those changes.

Contacting us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please email us at:  
Selenium Easy  

This document was last updated on December 24, 2013
